zenithbank.com 2016-05-05

# Home » Customer Services » Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy applies to all of the products, services and websites offered by Zenith Bank or its subsidiaries or affiliated companies collectively referred to as Zenith's "services". In addition, where more detailed information is needed to explain our privacy practices, we post supplementary privacy notices to describe how particular services process personal information. 

**Information we collect and how we use it**   
We understand that in the course of delivering our numerous banking service products to you via the net, we will come across certain information pertaining to your good self which, to our mind, are purely personal and may even be classified information but for the existing relationship which dictates that you shall either fill them in and/or divulge same in order to be linked to our site. Zenith will handle the information in this manner: 

**Information you provide**  
When you sign up for any Zenith Online Solution or other Zenith service or promotion that requires registration, we ask you for personal information (such as your name, email address and an account password). For certain services, such as our payment services, we require your debit or credit card information. We typically do not store this information and when we do, we maintain the data in encrypted form on secure servers. We may combine the information you submit under your account with information from other Zenith services or third parties in order to provide you with a better experience and to improve the quality of our services. For certain services, we may give you the opportunity to opt out of combining such information. 

**Log information**  
When you access Zenith services, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. 

**User communications**  
When you send email or other communications to Zenith, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services. 

**Affiliated sites**   
We offer some of our services in connection with other web sites e.g. Websites of our subsidiaries. Personal information that you provide to those sites may be sent to Zenith in order to deliver the service. We process such information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. The affiliated sites may have different privacy practices and we encourage you to read their privacy policies. 

**Other sites**  
This Privacy Policy applies to Zenith services only. We do not exercise control over the sites displayed or linked from within our various services. These other sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you. 

Zenith only processes personal information for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy and/or the supplementary privacy notices for specific services. In addition to the above, such purposes include:   
   • Providing our services to users, including the display of customized content;   
   • Auditing, research and analysis in order to maintain, protect and improve our services;   
   • Ensuring the technical functioning of our network; and   
   • Developing new services. 

You can find more information about how we process personal information by referring to the supplementary privacy notices for particular services. 

**Choices for personal information**  
When you sign up for a particular service that requires registration, we ask you to provide personal information. If we use this information in a manner different than the purpose for which it was collected, then we will ask for your consent prior to such use. 

If we propose to use personal information for any purposes other than those described in this Privacy Policy and/or in the specific service privacy notices, we will offer you an effective way to opt out of the use of personal information for those other purposes. We will not collect or use sensitive information for purposes other than those described in this Privacy Policy and/or in the supplementary service privacy notices, unless we have obtained your prior consent. 

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. 

You can decline to submit personal information to any of our services, in which case Zenith may not be able to provide those services to you. 

**Information sharing**  
Zenith only shares personal information with other companies or individuals in the following limited circumstances:   
   • We have your consent. We require opt-in consent for the sharing of any sensitive personal   
      information   
   • We provide such information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies or other trusted businesses or   
      persons for the purpose of processing personal information on our behalf. We require that these   
      parties agree to process such information based on our instructions and in compliance with this   
      Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.   
   • We have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is   
      reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable   
      governmental request, (b) enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential   
      violations thereof, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or (d)   
      protect against imminent harm to the rights, property or safety of Zenith, its users or the public as   
      required or permitted by law.   
   • If Zenith becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets,   
      we will provide notice before personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different   
       privacy policy. 

**Data integrity**  
Zenith processes personal information only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with this Privacy Policy or any applicable service-specific privacy notice. We review our data collection, storage and processing practices to ensure that we only collect, store and process the personal information needed to provide or improve our services. We take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we process is accurate, complete, and current, but we depend on our users to update or correct their personal information whenever necessary. 

**Accessing and updating personal information**  
When you use Zenith services, we make good faith efforts to provide you with access to your personal information and either to correct this data if it is inaccurate or to delete such data at your request if it is not otherwise required to be retained by law or for legitimate business purposes. We ask individual users to identify themselves and the information requested to be accessed, corrected or removed before processing such requests, and we may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive or systematic, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, or would be extremely impractical (for instance, requests concerning information residing on backup tapes), or for which access is not otherwise required.
